Hello everyone, I am the designer of Marvelous Designer, Hazel.
Tonight, we will bring you two lessons on how to make two styles of small horses in Marvelous Designer.
Next to us is our old friend, Ms. Shirley.
Ms. Shirley will answer your questions in the comments in my live stream.
There will also be a draw at the end of our live stream.
At the same time, you can also get our official WeChat red envelopes for free.
In the first half of the video, I will explain how to make these two small horses.
Ms. Shirley will explain in the last part of the video,
how to make the final look of Marvelous Designer.
Okay, let's get started.
First of all, the first one is our balloon small horse.
Okay.
Our balloon small horse is made up of many balloon sections.
So, first of all, we will make a rectangular board.
Then, we will use the cologne layer to give it a cologne layer.
Then, we will turn the surface over.
Then, we will reduce its particle strength and charge thickness.
Then, we will give it a little more pressure.
At this time, when we turn on the simulation, it will become a solid small pillow shape.
Then, we will remove the sewing line on both sides of it.
Change the sewing method of the long side of it to fold.
It will become a tube shape.
Then, add two short sides to the elasticity.
Give a ratio of 25.
It will shrink into a shape like a ham sausage.
Then, we will reduce its particle strength and charge thickness.
Let its elasticity become better.
And increase its bending strength.
Oh, no. Reduce its bending strength.
So that it can produce more small wrinkles.
This way, it will look more like the shape of a balloon skin.
After changing the properties, we will simulate it and take a look.
I feel that the elastic is not enough.
So, I reduced the strength of the cologne.
Then, change its weight.
I changed the weight to a little lighter.
Because balloons are very light.
It becomes a shape like a long QQ.
Then, we can start to use this basic balloon section to create the structure of the horse's body.
First, create two pairs of horse's legs.
Then, the body of the horse.
Then, the tail of the horse and the neck.
Hello, long QQ.
Then, we can copy its head and two ears.
Then, we can copy its special hair on its back.
Then, we can copy its declared body.
Then we can copy its 중요한 edging.
Then, we can change the length of the balloon parts.
Then, we can copy its hang.
Let it covered an value in the shape of the horse's liver.
Quickly modify.
In a few moments, we can start sewing.
Because of its legs.
Actually, in our everyday life, it is a Україnen side leg.
90 initiatives!
long balloons are constantly twisted and tied to make these body structures.
So the upper and lower legs of our legs are all sewn together.
To sew each balloon section to where it should be.
The head of the horse is sewn up with the body and the ears.
Sometimes when sewing fast, there may be a mistake in the sewing line, which is that the balloon is twisted.
You can right-click on the sewing line and then switch it over.
After checking that these sewing lines are sewn, we can start to simulate the combination of the horse's body.
Then we can start to simulate the combination of the horse's body.
Then we will combine the three medium-sized balloon sections together.
Then we stand up the horse lying on the ground.
Turn his legs in the right direction.
And his ears.
Also turned to the wrong direction.
Then you can start to freeze some panels.
And create'm turns'.
Now we will help theagedou style.
There are three CHARختA WITHING your accident body modeling project.
At the end at the next page a carannhaire made a reverse Slimming session.
像一个皮筋一样,箍住了小马的鼻子,让他有一种小马的脸的感觉。
然后把他的耳朵也缝纫起来了。
这个是前面忘记缝纫起来了,
他的耳朵应该是像他的腿部一样,上下都是缝纫起来的这种结构。
怎么会?
然后这边呢,我是给他的综毛部分去加了两个连接部件。
因为如果我们直接把这个综毛部分连接到小马的身体上的话,
他的那个耳朵跟脖子之间,还有身体跟脖子之间的缝隙太深了,
会导致这个综毛这个部位的变形。
所以我们需要两个不带压力的细小的连接部件。
来替代我们的综毛部分塞到这些间隙里。
我们把这两个连接件给它缝纫起来。
缝纫到这个综毛的两边。
是的,这个气球小马其实就是我们平时更常见的气球小狗的一个变体。
是把小狗的耳朵变小,然后把那个小狗的背上加上综毛。
还有一个很重要的地方就是,
然后它的脖子好像也是比平时的气球小狗更长一点的。
然后我们把这两个连接件缝到它脖子的缝隙里面。
然后调整了一下这个背上综毛的大小。
然后综毛的中间部分还是有一点不太贴小马的身体,所以我在这里藏了一个固定针。
然后我要把小马的脸部这一部分变成那个气球的弯弯的底。
所以我把这一部分的弹性给取消掉,然后将它们缝合到了一起。
然后用深层圆顺曲线把它的鼻子部分给它调圆。
然后我觉得只用深层圆顺曲线它鼻子好像还是有点方方的,所以又用曲线点单独调了一下。
然后制作好了我们小马的脸部部分,就开始制作我们气球尾巴那个打结的部分了。
先制作出一条长方形的板片。
然后开始我们的打结。
给我们的板片的两侧都打上整排的固定针。
然后在中间也打上一些方便调整的固定针。
然后开始我们的打结。
这样子在两边加上整排固定针。
让整排固定针的好处呢就是我们可以去旋转这个板片的两侧。
这样可以更加方便我们去在打结的时候穿过一些小小的缝隙。
然后我这边给了这个打结的板片一个新的织物。
然后将它的摩擦系数调高。
这样我们在拉紧这个结的时候,它的速度就会变得慢一些就不那么容易被拉散。
After the knot is finished, we can delete the part that is too long on both sides
Then sew the knot to the tail of the horse
Then we use a fixed needle to fix the knot
Then reduce the contact thickness to 1
Note that when I created this version, I changed its particle diameter
But I didn't change its contact thickness
I kept its contact thickness at 2.5
Then I copied it to make it a double-layer knot
Before copying, I changed its contact thickness to 1
In this way, if you don't copy, the contact thickness between the cloth and the cloth will be 1.5
In this way, when I use the function of the cloning layer to clone the inside layer
There is a gap between the cloth and the cloth
When copying again, it is not so easy to conflict
It is not so easy to penetrate
Then there is a kind of instability
And the knot will not fall off
Increase friction
Increase friction can make the cloth
When you tighten the knot, it will become slower
Then it will reduce the possibility of it penetrating directly
Then we put the finished inside layer on the small horse's butt
Then continue to adjust it a little more naturally
Because I feel that this knot is a little too big
So I gave it a tail-like shrinkage
Make this knot smaller
Then continue to freeze the knot part
Then simulate the tail of the small horse
Reduce the elastic ratio of these two short sides to it
Make it look more like being tightened
More natural
Make it more like being tightened
Make it more natural
Then we unroll all the panels for a short simulation
Make the relationship between the fabric and the fabric more correct
After confirming the shape, we can start to make the material of this little horse
Here I chose a color on the MD icon for the little horse
I wish you a successful New Year's Eve
Then change its material to plastic
Then increase its surface strength
Reduce its roughness
Then I uploaded a copper-plated sticker as the use of the little horse's eyes
Then when we use this kind of sticker, we can open it at the intersection
This pattern can be used across two panels
Then we remove the plastic
To make these sewing lines on the surface of the little horse not so much affected
So I connect all these sewing lines to it
It looks more like a balloon without a gap
把它朝向我们这一面的缝纫箱都给合并掉
然后背面的部分呢因为我们现在只有一个版片了已经绕了一圈了
但我们依然可以让它就是变得不明显一点
我刚刚是删掉了缝纫线上的那个缝纫线上的法线贴图
它就会变得更加不明显一点
然后我们在同一个版片中呢
目前我们软件中如果是同一个版片上的它的贴图
它放上去就算开启在接缝处它也没办法直接跨版片使用
所以大家可以再复制一个然后自己拼一下
然后这边我应用了一个四边形网格画
这样可以让我们的模型表面变得更加顺滑一点
好这样子我们的气球小马就已经制作完成了